handster.com 2007-12-10

# Handster.com - Windows Mobile Software for HTC, iPAQ, i-mate, MDA, Cingular 8125 and other Pocket PC.

Because we gather information about the customers of Handster.com we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions for use of that information.

Handster.com gathers the following information about users: 

  * Data that users provide through registration; 
  * Tracking information derived from web logs of our website. Such information enables us to better tailor our content to readers' needs and help advertisers better understand the demographics of our audience. 

**Handster does share the following information with the software that are available through the online store:**

  * Name 
  * Address 
  * Email Address 
  * Telephone 
  * Fax 
  * Software Purchased 
  * Software Registration Code (where applicable) 

This information is provided on the contractual understanding with each software publisher that it is to be used solely and exclusively for the purpose of tracking customer software registrations and providing technical support, as is the standard practice in the industry.

Handster.com does not provide this information to any other third parties under any circumstances.

In case of questions, please send mail to [contact@handster.com](mailto:contact@handster.com).

Handster.com offers free electronic newsletters to users. We gather the e-mail addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Customers may remove themselves from any mailing list by following the instructions contained in every newsletter. They can also subscribe to the newsletters at the time of registration. 

Handster.com may occasionally conduct customer surveys to better target our content and product inventory to our audience. We may share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our advertisers and partners. We never share any information about specific individuals with any third party, except as noted previously.

Handster tracks user traffic throughout Handster.com. Overall usage statistics, according to a user's domain name, browser type and MIME type is tracked.

Handster.com also tracks and catalogs the search terms that customers enter into our search tools, but this tracking is never associated with individual users.

Handster.com uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience in our website, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.

Handster uses information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters and enable users to participate in polls and message boards. We send out newsletters to subscribers on a monthly schedule and occasionally send out special editions when we think subscribers might be particularly interested in something we are doing. Handster never shares newsletter mailing lists with any third parties, including advertisers or partners.

We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. Handster does not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.

We track search terms entered in our search function as one of many measures of what interests our users. But we don't track which terms a particular user enters.

Handster.com creates aggregrate reports on traffic for advertisers and partners. This allows our advertisers to advertise more effectively and allows our users to receive advertisements that are relevant to their needs. Handster never shares individual personal information with anyone, so an advertiser will never know that a specific user clicked their advertisement.

Handster uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our audience demographics. We do not share information about individual users with any third party, with the exceptions noted previously.

A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such including a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Handster.com uses cookies to track the items you add to your shopping card and to enforce security rules regarding software that you download.

If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie.

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser.

Handster.com gives users options wherever necessary and practical, such choices include: 

  * Opting not to receive our electronic newsletters when registering for a site 
  * Opting not to provide certain personal information when registering for a site or service 
  * Opting not to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need for any information from our users 

For example, if you register with us but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our registration for. You may also update your preferences at any time by accessing our member information area. 

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by Handster.com website. The website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy policy of such other websites. 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on in this area of our Web site. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed. We will provide the new policy on our web server and additionally we will provide a link to the old privacy statement.

Your continued usage of our server will mean you accept those changes.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web Sites.

Users may unsubscribe to any of our electronic newsletters at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of each newsletter.

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at [contact@handster.com](mailto:contact@handster.com).

Version: 1.0, online since: April 30, 2005
